I want him, but I don't need him.
And that's what we're here to say,
is that we are the new Black Panther Party.
What's the biggest problem facing the movement?
Well, you know, we're supposed to be in this era
of so-called post-racial harmony with all people in America,
but us blacks are being murdered all over the place,
and we get the same treatment time and time again.
We're not even second-class citizens.
We third-class.
Stand up,
Black America,
and declare to white America
that we ain't gonna take this no more, okay?
Why come out now and say this?
You know what?
You have 400 years to get it right, America,
but you don't know how to treat your people,
all people.
It's time to stand up.
It's time to take back.
It's time for us to fight back.
And we don't take your phony words anymore.
We're not gonna do it.
We want concrete results.
You know, you hear what we're saying to you,
United Snakes of America?
What are you supposed to do when the whole world is watching
and no one is saying anything?
We will not be silent.
Okay, you, sir, anything you wanted to say?
Oh, me?
No, I'm good.
Eight kilos.
100% pure-grade Afghani heroin.
Dip.
$100,000 U.S.
dollars.
Hold up.
We should count it first.
You know,
we're gonna do a straight count on this right now.
Count it, count it.
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
Mm-hmm.
We should probably do it fast,
so we don't make our friends here wait.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
20,
40,
60,
80,
100,
20,
40, 60,
80,
200.
You know what?
I'm fast.
Let me just do it.
I'll take care of that.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Why are you doing piles of 9?
It's faster than tens.
Oh, really?
I do my nines 10 times,
and then I do an extra pile of 10.
Faster.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, we should probably both be counting.
Oh,
well,
this is good too,
if there's double trouble.
All right.
And 20, 40, 60, 80, 100, 20, 40, 60.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Can you do something over there, please?
It's a little distracting.
Oh, you know what?
What's that?
I got it.
We could time me.
Okay, we time me counting out 1,000.
We take that time, and then we just count money
for that time times 100.
Que as destos pendeles.
No, I got it.
This is it right here.
I'm gonna do a web search for a picture of $100,000,
okay?
Then,
you know,
we'll know what it's supposed to look like,
and then we can arrange our money to look exactly like it,
and see here.
Hey, here we go.
Right here, look.
I mean, damn,
that looks just like a lot like our money.
I think we got $100,000 here, folks.
I think we made it.
You know what?
That is our money.
I'm sorry.
Earlier, when we were counting,
I took a picture of our money
so I could upload it on Yahoo Answers.
Oh, damn.
That's right.
I just wanted to see if anyone could verify
what $100,000 looked like.
Oh, you got it.
What was I thinking?
I got it, man.
Go, go, go, go.
I got it.
What the hell you doing, man?
You know, I was gonna try to Rain Man it.
Well, that's a plan right there.
That's right.
Okay.
Yeah, here we go.
Here we go.
Okay.
Yep,
I got that.
$99,980.
Oh,
yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
I actually pressed it already.
The walk button, I pressed it.
Couldn't hurt to press it again.
But it won't help.
I mean,
I pressed it already, right?
It's already done.
You don't think I didn't press it?
No, I wasn't saying that.
Good,
because I most certainly did press it.
Just have to wait for the change.
I'm,
like,
late for work,
so I'm just gonna press it.
What for?
Why would you do something that's already done?
I mean, I just think that that's crazy,
right?
I don't know.
You wouldn't suit up and try to kill Bin Laden again.
It's done.
I have killed the Bin Laden of pressing this button.
How long ago did you press it?
What do you think?
I've been standing here for days.
I just pressed it right as you walked up.
Are you sure you pressed it?
Am I sure I pressed it?
It's how could I miss it?
Rats know how to press buttons.
Do you think I'm dumber than a rat?
No. No, nobody's saying anything like that.
It's gonna change.
Just wait.
It's because I pressed it already.
Okay, no offense.
I'm just gonna press it.
What would you do that for?
This is precision equipment
designed by people with engineering degrees.
It will work.
I pressed it, sir.
I pressed the button.
While we've been standing here,
the light cycle has gone by twice, okay?
I'm not saying you didn't press it.
I'm just saying maybe it didn't work.
If it didn't work for me,
why in the world would it work for you?
You think that it would change faster if you pressed it?
You think the light doesn't like me or something?
Or do you think that this particular button was designed
so that it only works after the second time that it's been pressed?
It's that lunacy, okay?
Do you understand?
Do not cut my balls off on this one, okay?
Please
do not press the button again.
Okay,
fine.
We'll just
stand here.
Thank you.
What?
Hey, no!
Oh!
I told you I shouldn't have pressed the button.
I told him not to do it.
No, actually, I already pressed the button.
Rick Nicholsby reporting live from a gruesome scene.
A cult known as QET, or Quest for Eternal Truth,
has apparently taken their own lives in a mass suicide.
Police confirmed that cyanide-laced cherry Kool-Aid
was also on the premises.
Excuse me.
Hi. Rick Nicholsby, Channel 6.
Hi. Are you two from the neighborhood?
Uh, yes.
No.
Yeah.
Okay,
were you two members of the cult that lived here?
The cult?
What cult?
Was this a cult?
I had no idea this was a cult.
Although I want to say the term cult is a little judgmental.
I would say the same thing.
Not knowing the full doctrine.
Well,
apparently they believed that there was a spaceship
waiting for them behind the moon.
Okay,
well,
you know,
that still is really possible.
I mean, it's possible, right?
Who knows what is out there in the universe?
It could be behind the moon.
Okay, well, it appears they killed themselves
in order to board the ship.
Right,
and that's where we disagreed with them,
right there.
Or would have.
We would have disagreed with them
had we been there on our departure day.
Their departure day! Their departure day!
Which is the day that they did this.
I mean,
that's what you could call it if you wanted to.
But I ain't in no cult.
I mean,
what I always wondered is how or am starting to wonder,
since you brought this to our attention,
why if there was a spaceship in the sky,
why wouldn't it just beam us up?
Beam them up.
Right, just beam them up.
Just beam them up.
Why can't you just beam them up alive?
Why you got to be there to get beamed up?
You know what I'm saying?
I've been saying that for weeks,
seconds,
for seconds,
because you,
Rick,
Nichols B.,
you told us that,
you know,
and that's how I knew.
Fifteen seconds ago.
You said it.
I didn't know anything about it
until you had said it,
because I ain't in no cult.
Okay, well then why would someone join a cult?
Charismatic leader.
You know, like a compelling person.
Taco Tuesday.
I mean,
hypothetically,
they could have had tacos on Tuesday,
which would have been a draw.
I mean, that would have been a plus.
Okay,
so this is a tragic day for this community and
for the members of the quest for Earthly Truth.
I'm Rick Nichols B. reporting.
You see?
Everybody jump the gun!
We're ready!
Best comic book adaptation to film, hands down.
No argument.
See you later, girls.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
Um,
I know I'm in the minority here,
but I don't really like the Christopher Nolan Batman movies.
I don't.
I really just feel like
I'm overrated.
Okay.
Well,
that's, um, that's just an opinion, you see?
That's why I prefaced it by saying,
I know I'm in the minority.
Awkward.
You know what?
No. No.
Not really.
It's not awkward.
At least not until you said awkward.
Now it's awkward because of what you said.
Anyway.
Anyway what?
Really.
Because when you say anyway,
then you have to follow it up with an actual
contribution to the conversation we're having.
Yikes.
No. Look at me.
Look at me.
There's no yikes.
And the reason why there's no yikes is because
there's nothing scary about this situation.
Okay?
It's a very low-stake situation.
Alright.
No. Not alright.
Come here.
No. Don't look at him.
Don't look at either of those guys.
Look at me.
Alright?
Alright what?
Because after you say alright,
you have to follow that up with something.
Don't do it.
Don't look at them.
Do not look at them.
No. No. Do not look at them.
Don't do it.
Tell us how you really feel.
I'll tell you how I really feel.
Listen.
I really feel like you're an asshole
who has nothing interesting to say.
So what?
Ow. No. Don't.
No. Don't look at him.
Come here.
Turn it.
Right here.
Tell me an opinion that you have about something.
Just one opinion that you have about anything at all.
Just share an opinion.
Anything.
Share an opinion.
Share an opinion right now.
Just on the top of your head.
Share an opinion.
Anything.
Just one opinion.
That's all I'm asking.
Share one opinion right now.
Share an opinion.
I don't have an opinion.
That's why I just like everything that
everyone else likes in pop culture.
Don't look at me.
Okay.
Hey, man.
This is your first time?
No, man.
I've been doing zombie extra work on
this show since day one first season,
man.
My first time.
Oh, it's your first time on this show?
My first time being extra at all.
Ever?
Kind of nervous.
Oh, wow.
Okay, man.
Hey, man.
Sorry about you.
You'll be all right, man.
It's okay, man.
It's not that hard, man.
You'll be all right.
Me personally,
dude,
I'm looking for that lunge bump though.
What's a lunge bump?
Oh, that's like if you get featured,
if you lunge at somebody,
and then you get a bump in your pay.
And if you're really lucky,
man,
they blow your head off,
that's straight bank right there.
All right, extras!
I'm the assistant director.
Gather round.
Jerry,
I had a thought,
man,
about the first scene
that y'all was doing.
Not now, Stan.
Oh, Steve.
It's Steve.
Okay.
I'm gonna need somebody to lunge at the fence.
Ah!
You think you can handle it?
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
It's his first day, though.
He's kind of nervous, man.
He's kind of nervous.
It's his first day.
Okay, so the director's gonna yell, action.
Mac's gonna come by,
and then you're just gonna lunge into the fence,
like,
rah!
You want me to say, gra?
Oh, this is crazy.
Say whatever.
Okay, all right, cool, man.
Hey, you know, hey, that's cool.
Hey, you know, I got a lot more experience, man.
You can just use me.
I've been here day one, first season.
So, okay, cool.
All right, that's fine.
You're gonna go with him.
All right, good for you, man.
Good for you.
Gra?
No, don't do it.
You don't have to say gra.
Do whatever the hell you want to do, man.
That's the lunge bump.
That is the lunge bump, man.
You got it.
You got it on your first day.
Ever bein' an extra ever.
You got it, man.
Good for you.
And action.
What the hell was that?
Cut!
Oh,
man,
I would be more than happy to fill in,
man.
I'd be more than happy to step in.
Mac,
just remember when you're coming through the factory
that, like, your mind is still in the car.
I mean,
you all got to pick people based on qualifications,
man.
Okay.
You can't just be pickin' random people.
It's a good note.
Good note.
But maybe what I was doing sort of superseded that.
Agreed.
Yeah, we were just discussing that.
Absolutely, it supersedes it.
Yeah, but, uh,
let's do one that just seeds it, okay?
Just same level.
We're goin' again.
Straight away, okay?
Wow. Okay.
Reset.
Okay.
He's not doing a good job at it.
You're doin' great, though, man.
Opportunity knocks.
You gotta answer the door, man.
And action.
Hey.
Meep,
meep,
meep.
Cut!
I'd be more than happy to step in.
At any time you want me to,
I'd be more than happy to do it.
Just a certain sense of urgency is all we're looking for.
Clock's ticking.
You got survivors to find, right?
Can't tell y'all if it's something real significant.
This dude right here is not doing what a zombie does.
This dude was literally on our last take
waving his hand up in the air like this, Jerry,
making beaker sounds.
He sounded like beaker from the Muppets, y'all.
Thank you.
That's great.
Just a ticking clock on this.
This is all we're looking for because there are survivors.
This is what we're after.
Okay.
I find the ambivalence in there.
The ambivalence is art.
It's gorgeous, and we love it.
But there are zombies,
so if we could just pick up the pace
just a hair, that'd be great.
Straight away, please.
Right away.
Jerry, Jerry, Jerry.
We're not doin'
a night of the living Muppets, are we?
We are not.
Because the beaker is not a zombie.
Do you have any notes?
Yeah, don't be a f***ing beaker.
Quiet, please.
Action.
I'm gonna eat your brain,
zombie.
Cut. No!
He actually just said the word zombie!
Come on, man.
You ever hear a zombie say the word zombie before?
No, you haven't.
I don't think so.
You know what?
Get rid of this kid.
Thank you.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry,
dog,
but you're terrible at this,
man.
Hey, man, no, he talking about him.
No.
He talking about him because he said zombie.
Thank you, Steve.
No, you want me to leave?
Hey,
man,
I've been up here staggering around here
for three and a half years,
and I've been startling extras left and right.
When do I get to startle the lead, huh?
One more for safety.
Straight away.
Here we go.
Still rolling.
Action.
Hey,
what do we do if we had to go to the bathroom?
We like it?
I love it.
Genius.
Moving on.
Thank you, honey.
The new Earth from Space, our Muppets!
Yellow Falcon, what do your senses tell you?
He's struck to us as a killing machine.
His armor is impervious to our blasters.
You got any ideas, Red Falcon?
Sure do, Yellow Falcon.
Blue Falcon,
you remember our battle at Dango Bluff?
I'll take the legs, you take the blasters.
It was Beaver Creek and I took the legs.
Are you sure of that flank, Black Falcon?
Um,
are you talking to me because
I'm the Green Falcon?
No time for that, Black Falcon.
Purple Falcon, arm missiles.
Roger that.
Arming missiles now.
Uh... Battle formations, we're going in.
Hey. Roger that.
Hold up.
Copy that.
My Falcon is green.
Hey,
hey,
we can talk about our Falcon colors
when we get back to base, Black Falcon.
Right now we got a mission to do.
Fall into Falcon formation.
Well,
here's the issue is that you're gonna give me an order,
I'm not gonna know you're talking to me.
Because I'm not in the Black Falcon.
Come on, chill it out, Black Falcon.
Yeah, Black Falcon, relax.
First of all,
I don't like the way you guys are saying Black.
Second of all, there is no Black Falcon.
I'm Green Falcon.
Black Falcon,
homie,
no one's trying to get up in your grill here.
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh, don't talk to me like that.
No, don't say grill like that.
I'm the Green Falcon, and I...
Stopping so Black Falcon about it.
What the f*** do you mean by that?
Black Falcon,
brother,
I understand what you're going through.
Do you?
No, I don't think you do.
How would you feel if I called you Red Falcon,
huh?
Whoa.
And Purple Falcon, how would you feel
if I called you Yellow Falcon, huh?
That's racist.
That was racist.
Yeah, that's racist.
Oh, that is racist.
That's racist?
Oh,
see?
Okay, nope, forget it.
Black Falcon out.
Green Falcon!
Green Falcon! Damn it!
Hey,
why'd that Green Falcon fall out of Falcon Formation?
Black Falcon, get on that and report back.
Black Falcon.
Black Falcon, come in.
Blazing Earth from space.
Power Falcons!
Excuse me, Big Man, Big Man, Big Man.
Excuse me, Big Man, no.
But Big Man, okay?
God bless you.
I'll catch you on the up-flip.
Thank you, Big Man. Thank you, Big Man.
Hey, brother.
Hey.
Can I ask you a question real quick,
though,
brother man?
Oh,
see,
that's good,
because I was about to ask you a question.
Okay, so here's the deal, man.
Crazy thing, my car went out of gas.
About a mile up the road,
that's the way I was just wondering if I get a little bit of money.
You know, just get a couple of gallons.
Okay, that's crazy, because you know what?
My car had also broke down right up the road.
I got my daughter here.
She fine.
She's sleeping in the car.
I got to get back to her real quick.
So if you could help me out...
I was going to ask you if you could help me.
Let me just give you my wallet out here and show you my ID
to let you know that I am straight up legit.
Real, I ain't trying to do nothing to nobody.
On the issue of legitimacy,
I too have an identification.
That's an employee ID from Borders Bookstore.
You see right here,
I got my Bali's Total Fitness ID right here.
It shows you that I stay fit and conscientious and whatnot.
You also notice that these other IDs I have in my hand
have the same name on it,
which makes you know that it is indeed me.
Okay,
I too have multiple IDs crescendoing in this.
Duh duh duh duh, yogurt lamb punch card.
Okay, yeah, I see that right there.
That is almost my ninth purchase, apparently,
and you can't pay for that.
Yeah.
All right,
so normally I would not ask another person
for assistance, but our family is in a
fiduciary crisis
right now.
My wife is languishing in the hospital.
She a construction worker, and what happened is
she got struck in the face by a power line,
fried her whole head up,
burnt both her eyeballs out.
She's getting eyeball replacement surgery as we speak.
I also have a spousal injury crisis on my midst as well.
My wife was in the astronaut program,
making her a full-fledged astronaut.
Okay, impressive.
And she had gotten
moon dust in her lungs,
and hell,
you don't want to get no...
That's never good.
It's never good.
We don't want that.
So maybe we could find an ATM
or something like that.
Oh, look, that's one over there.
Guys, what's the chances of it?
We should probably check that out.
Yeah, let's just take a look right there.
Well, here we are.
ATM machines that I did not know previously were here.
All right, two of them no less.
I'll tell you what we should do, though, man.
You give me the 20, okay?
I'll give you the three that's on my person,
then I will give you the 17 after.
Then you give me that 17. Uh-huh.
I'll cut you a check for 100 just to cover that.
You give me the change in cash.
Okay, okay.
I feel that.
Why am I playing?
I'm just gonna give you my ATM card
so you know I'm legit.
Sure, sure.
Of course, of course.
I'm gonna give you my ATM card so we both have something of value
from the other person.
All right.
And your code is?
It is 1234, and yours, sir?
12345. All right, thank you.
Okay, that is a Ralph's Rewards card.
Okay,
that is a credit card placeholder you would find
in a translucent sleeve in a brand-new wallet.
Excuse me, big man.
Can I ask you a question, biggest of men?
I got a question right quick.
Oh!
You gotta let me out of here.
Oh, okay.
You tricked me.
I can honestly say I wasn't trying to trick you.
You weren't?
All I said was you gotta let me out of here.
There's no trick.
So I do have to let you out of here?
Yes. Okay.
Bon voyage.
Orders to let him go.
I don't know why he's in here in the first place.
I don't know.
Oh!
Hey!
What?
You really got me in trouble.
Sorry.
Yeah, you must think I'm stupid.
Well, I'm not stupid.
I'm smart.
So, you know.
You know how you can prove that you're really smart?
Oh, yeah.
Let me guess.
You want me to let you out of here again?
Well...
You know what?
You think you can trick me into letting you out again?
Well, you can't.
Because this is my choice.
Get the heck out of here.
All right.
All right?
Reverse psychology.
Hey, I'm sorry about that, guys.
That was me, guys.
My bad.
Real nice.
Now they said they were gonna dock my pay,
and if I let you out of here again,
then I'm gonna be severely punished.
I'm actually surprised they haven't
already thrown you in here with me.
No, prison is for bad guys.
You're a bad guy, and I'm a good guy.
Yeah, but you can see how, from my perspective,
I'm a good guy.
Wait, you're a good guy?
Oh, my gosh.
It doesn't seem like you understand what your job is.
Oh, okay.
I see what you're doing.
You're trying to manipulate me with reverse psychology.
Well, it's not gonna work.
No, no, no.
It's not even worth going out there again.
Look,
they're just gonna get me and bring me back in here,
just like they always do.
No.
Unless...
What?
No,
I'm...
Forget it.
I don't want to take advantage of you anymore.
Look, hey, no, listen.
I'm not gonna fall for it.
Whatever it is,
it may as well just tell me.
I was just gonna say that, like,
if you were to help me...
Uh-huh.
...get past the guards...
Yeah, yeah.
...and get all the way out...
I really...
No, I have to tell you.
You need to think about this long and hard.
Mm-hmm.
Weigh your options
and consider the ramifications of those options.
Like heck, I will.
Let's go.
All right.
I'm busting you out of here!
Don't yell, man.
You're gonna as well ring the alarm, man.
That's a good idea, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Where were we?
Ah!
Oh, hi, Tom. What's the hell?
Gotta see you guys.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
I did it again, didn't I?
I was in prison...
a guard.
I was a prison guard.
I wasn't allowed to talk to the prisoners.
That was the thing.
They said to me,
if you talk to those prisoners,
you're gonna get trouble.
You're gonna get trouble.
Now that I'm in here, I'm gonna talk to my son.
I'm gonna talk to my son.
Any arrangement?
What are we doing in this neighborhood?
Come on.
This place is in our price range.
Besides,
I mean,
people say the neighborhood's turning around.
Who the fuck here?
It's Jordan and Kira.
We're here to view the apartment at three.
Oh, shit.
My bad.
I had this homeless crackhead
trying to set up house in here yesterday.
Almost had to beat his ass.
But y'all ain't got nothing to worry about,
because anybody try to get up in here,
I will murder them.
Let me get y'all to tour.
We got these vintage windows.
They've been here as long as the building been here.
Oh, shit.
Get away from the window! Get away from the window!
Hey!
You mother-in-law, I see you out there!
You get out that car, and I will murder you!
That's what I thought.
So roll on, little...
Roll on!
My nephew, Craig.
You're a good kid.
You smoke crack, though.
It's just in case he come back.
Now, I filed a serial number off there,
so if you got to shoot anybody,
just make sure to wipe your fingerprints off this mother-in-law.
Well, come on, y'all.
I ain't gonna bite you.
Brand-new cupboards.
I put the contact paper in myself here
so y'all don't get no germs.
Get down!
What was that you had?
All right.
Oh.
Nah, ain't no thing.
I thought Craig was rolling back.
I ain't getting shot by this mother-in-law twice.
Damn.
While we down here, check this out.
Original hardwood floor from when the building was built.
Check out this green, brother.
Ooh, that is craftsmanship.
Anyway, come on.
Sit down.
This paint is all new.
Oh, shit.
Okay, this happened after I had painted.
Funny story.
We got crackheads in this neighborhood,
and one of them living right next door here,
right?
And one day,
he was smoking crack,
just went looney tunes,
and mistook his 9-millimeter,
that's a pistol,
honey,
for the remote control.
But don't worry.
You ain't never gonna see him again.
Ain't nobody ever
gonna see him...
again.
Plus, I'm gonna put a fancy little hook in there
and turn it into a hat rack.
Now, let's take a look at this bedroom.
What the...
I ain't found this place first!
Found it, man! I own this place!
Can y'all give me a second?
You'll break me, mother...
I will cut you with my sword, King!
What's going on?
So,
that's gonna be first month of last month rent,
one month security deposit.
I'll get the paperwork started.
Okay, baby, let's hit this rock real quick.
Father, please hear our prayer for the poor.
Thank you, Father, yes.
We beseech you for the disenfranchised,
the less fortunate,
and those that suffer.
Show us your will,
so we can continue to do your work.
Yes, Father, please.
I come to answer your prayer.
Listen carefully to my instruction.
Hallelujah!
Oh my God!
Hey!
Thank you so much.
I want you to sell everything you own and
immediately begin service to the poor.
I just want to clarify, um,
everything?
Yes.
Read yourself of all earthly possessions.
Oh, ****! The house is haunted!
Go!
Go! Go!
This is hideous!
Oh,
I see what they did there.
This place is so nice.
This is supposed to be one of the best French places in town.
I did not realize that you were so cultured.
You're sweet.
My French is pretty good.
So, uh, I can order for both of us.
Oh! If you want.
Well, well, well.
Bonjour.
Welcome to Chez de la Montre-Bentre.
I am your waiter for this evening.
My name is Jean-Luc de la Pire Renaud.
But you may call me Jean.
Bonjour, Jean.
Oh, look at you!
If you have any questions about anything at all,
I'm more than happy to assist you.
Jean,
I got it.
Merci beaucoup.
Oh, très bien.
Well,
our first special tonight is un poisson du jour.
It's a loup de merblou en verre saut
served with a plumaire verte du cochon du plombon.
That is served on a bed of gendarmes de filisse au pain
and also served with luminette rouge
and soufflé petit de fiertes du pont de grenier.
Oh. Mm. Yum.
Our soup today is a bolard moissant
with just a dash of Chantin-Bardre
and served with melty pisson tonche-partre fleur.
Soup.
Yeah.
Our other seafood today,
we have a very nice flint-tempon
grande pince varte from the Goutte-Saint-Mousson Valley in Vézantin.
It is served with the side of colombo fontaner
de la matin du garde fleumier coulomb sauce.
Oh, man.
It's just...
I'm a little bit overwhelmed.
Ah, yes.
Oh, God. I'm so glad you said that.
I was about to say the same thing.
Okay,
so you would recommend getting the flint-tempon
grande pince varte du plomb de s'avère with the...
Ooh, I'm sorry.
Is the pilleuré-tide de pisseur roulant
and a heavy fonds-en-tents sauce?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's more like a cochon de contre-contre-vange sauce.
What do you think?
I'm gonna defer to him on this one
because he knows this stuff way better than I do.
Oh, thanks.
Monsieur?
What?
Um, yeah, we'll, uh, we'll have the...
Sonde...
I mean, the...
The...
I'm...
Chon...
Chon-nanta.
Au-tchois de fleur...
De florens en chon...
It's been nice knowing you have a lovely dinner.
I'm gonna make this really nice and easy for you.
I need names, and you're gonna give them to me.
You have to listen to me.
This is all a huge mistake.
Bull...
Apartment of Homeland Security's been monitoring your calls
for weeks, Rajiv.
We got you.
We know about you and your friends.
We know that you're a...
Terrorist! I am a terrorist!
We... Me and my friends, we breed dogs.
Specifically, terrorists.
We write terrorist fiction.
We-we-we spend a good deal of time discussing
possible future terrorist plots.
Ah!
Oh!
It's a nice try.
Really is.
But it's bull...
Rajiv!
Come on.
Is that the best you got?
Now, come on.
I'm listening.
Just tell me.
Tell me.
Tell me about this imminent attack.
What?
What attack?
I don't know what...
I don't know.
What are you talking...
What am I talking about?
I don't know, huh?
Huh?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you...
You don't know?
I don't know.
June 11th, Rajiv!
You spoke of an imminent attack.
Oh, oh, yes.
No, listen.
That was my friend.
Listen, his dog bit him.
No. And I told him, if you do not train them...
No. ...another terrorist attack is imminent.
Ah!
Oh!
So, you lied, and you see what happens?
I'm not lying to you.
Come on, Rajiv.
I like you.
Let's be friends, huh?
Now,
you still haven't explained to me why we found,
on the search engine of your computer,
the words, Target Washington, 49 times.
That is because I was in D.C.
for a dog show,
and I had to buy a squeezy toy, a birthday card,
and some deodorant,
all at an affordable price.
All right.
You can only do that at Target.
Yeah, okay.
I see how you want to play this.
Come on, come here.
This is not a case of mistaken identity, Rajiv.
And you know it.
We've heard the conversations between you and Jafar.
Were you discussing your hatred of American ideals?
The ideals of ideas,
American ideals.
I hate them.
They were for a dancing queen.
It was a desecration to our path.
My favorite band.
We got you on tape referring to Jafar
as one of the architects of...
7-Eleven!
It was 7-Eleven.
Jafar, he designs convenience stores.
7-Eleven.
Oh, sh...
Wilson,
65 dogs just attacked the Capitol Building.
Were they terriers?
How did you know?
Praise Abba!
It is so good to see you, Keith.
Yeah,
we usually have to wait for a special occasion.
Well, actually, I have a little surprise.
I got engaged.
Oh!
Oh,
son!
Oh, son.
Whoo-hoo!
Yes!
Wow!
Congratulations, little bro.
Engaged.
Kind of a big deal.
More for me, I guess.
That's what that means.
Yes, well, um...
She got a name?
Stephanie.
Marriage
is a wonderful journey.
50% on the divorce.
Sorry, bro.
Them's just the facts.
I will, uh, keep that in mind.
Thank you.
You got a photo?
Oh, yeah.
A.K.A.
Does she exist?
There you go.
Whistle.
Mmm! Ha-ha!
Oh,
she's beautiful.
Let me get eyes on this.
Everybody else already,
huh?
Great lighting.
Airbrush?
I know.
She kind of looks like that one model, uh,
on The Price is Right.
Uh, yes.
Uh, that's her.
The Price is Right, Clive!
That's your show.
Shut up, Ma!
No, it's not.
Uh, yeah.
Stephanie.
Mm-hmm.
People always underbid on her showcases.
Not the best presenter.
Where's the wedding?
Oh, uh, in Hawaii.
Oh! Yeah.
Oh-ho-ho!
Oh!
Awesome!
Whoo-hoo!
Melancholiki maca!
She ever been married before?
Uh, no.
So she says.
Ex-boyfriends, you got one?
Of course.
Sloppy seconds, at least.
Right, Dad?
Keith, she sounds wonderful.
Thank you, Mom. Shut up, Mom!
Silence from you!
Okay.
You're cut off from talking!
You know what, Clive?
I really don't appreciate the way that you're talking to Mom.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yes!
The prodigal son hath returned!
You know what?
You want to go?
Let's go!
Because I've been here for the last 15 years,
taking care of Mom and Dad while you've
been trollopsing all over the world!
And why?
So you can come back here and criticize me for how I treat them?
No. I actually came here
to ask you
if you would do me the honor of being my best man.
I know that we have, uh,
had our differences,
but you're my older brother.
We'll pay for your room.
And we're also gonna rent you a car.
And we'll pay to fly you out there.
First class.
Well, we can't afford first class.
Well, f*** you!
You're dead to me!
Why?
Shut up, Ma!
I'm eating in my room!
Well, that went better than expected.
I think so.
Yeah.
Hey man, how you doing there?
You guys got bow and arrows.
Yeah?
Oh,
yeah.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah, there it is.
There.
That'll do it.
That's gonna do it.
Yep. Where are the arrows at?
Yeah, you guys got M80s?
We don't carry fireworks.
Damn!
You have something else that's explosive
that I could tape to the end of an arrow?
We have shotgun shells,
but I feel I have to ask,
are you planning to attach those to arrows and use them as a weapon?
What?
No! What?
Are you crazy?
You think that would work though?
What if I shot two explosive arrows
through a window to break them open?
Sir,
I feel like I have to ask you what you're planning to use these for.
Oh, no.
I'm not planning to do anything.
I'm just Christmas shopping.
You got zip lines?
Nope.
But you got hooks and anchors and cables?
We got some of those things,
but I do not recommend manufacturing your own zip line.
Oh, I'm not doing that.
No.
Let's say somebody was manufacturing their own zip line.
Do you think if they had busted some
windows open on a building somehow,
then fired the zip line off a bow and arrow
and had attached to the wall of said building
that they could just ride the zip line into the building?
I have no idea, sir.
Whatever you're planning on doing,
please don't do it.
I'm not doing anything.
I'm just doing some Christmas shopping
and trying to get it out of the way.
Bow and arrow is from her nephew,
the zip line is from her grandmother,
et cetera and whatnot,
you know what I'm saying there?
It's no big deal.
Speaking of other things, do you guys have
just
the top half of a knight in armor?
First of all, it's called a suit of armor.
Oh, yep, that's it.
That's right.
That's what I meant to say.
We have one, but it's sold as a complete set.
Yep, yep.
Yep.
Well, the person is four.
They only need the top half.
They don't need the legs.
Mm-hmm.
Well, what if somebody was shooting at you?
What were the chances you think they'd try to shoot your legs?
I feel like I have to tell you that a suit of armor
will not deflect bullets.
I'll take my chances.
With Christmas.
Which brings me to my next question.
Do you guys have roller skates?
I think we have a pair around.
Uh-huh.
Let me ask you a question.
How fast do you think you have to be going on roller skates
to get past a couple of armed guards
and still be going fast enough to smash through a safe door?
One of those big bank safes?
No!
I don't know.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Uh,
hey, you guys got one of those, you know,
it's one of those big bags with a dollar sign on the side of it?
Okay.
Yep.
You're gonna shoot arrows with shotgun shells
attached to them to a bank window to blow out the glass,
then you're gonna shoot a zip line through that window,
and you're gonna slide on into the hallway.
You're gonna be wearing roller skates,
so you can just skate on past the armed guards
who will be shooting at you,
and you're gonna hope that they both won't hit your legs,
and if they are aiming at your torso,
the suit of medieval armor will deflect the bullets.
Then you're gonna hope to gather enough speed
to burst through the big bank vault at the end of the hallway
where you're gonna collect the money in a cartoon money bag.
Well,
no.
I'm just an uncle who's buying some sh-t for Christmas,
and I think I'll take my business elsewhere.
Merry Christmas.
It's April.
Neil?
Yes, honey?
Neil deGrasse Tyson,
I asked you to take the dog out for a walk.
I left the house four hours ago.
Now I come back,
and this little motherf-ckin' Sputnik
has done pissed on my drapes.
Now I've got to get rid of those things and get new ones.
Neil,
it doesn't make any sense.
You're an astrophysicist.
How can you not keep track of little details like this?
Well,
actually,
it's the little details
that cannot be kept track of by definition.
In 1927,
a German university lecturer named
Werner Heisenberg came to a seemingly paradoxical conclusion
that the more we know about the position of a particle
in physical space,
the less we know about its momentum
and vice versa.
Okay, but what...
Taken in conjunction with what we know about the expansion
of the universe,
this brings us to a fascinating possibility
that maybe what we experience as one point in time-space
could actually be a lesion of points,
which would mean that your curtains
and little Sputnik's pee-pee could be as distant from one another
as we are from the furthest galaxy.
Oh,
okay.
Well, just...
next time.
Of course, dear.
Neil!
There you are.
What are you doing?
We have to go to my Aunt Nellie's funeral.
How were you not ready?
I've been talking to you about this all week.
How am I gonna find you in your boxers
looking in a science magazine?
Oh, I swear, Neil,
sometimes I think you don't have any idea of what's important.
Well,
actually,
an idea of what's important is as close as we can ever come
to any definition of importance.
Our galaxy is one of over 100 billion in the observable universe.
And it's 100,000 light years across,
which means it would take light 100,000 years to traverse.
Okay, but...
But that's just space.
If we were to chart the history of the universe on one calendar year,
the history of mankind as we know it would just
take place in the final second of that year.
So,
whether I'm ready now or in 500 years,
well,
cosmically speaking,
the distinction is meaningless.
Well,
okay.
I'm going now.
Goodbye, honey.
Neil!
Who is she?
Who is the white bitch
that left this goddamn lipstick stain on your collar?
Hmm?
Oh, I got you.
You're caught.
Because this is apricot-colored.
And you know who wears that?
White bitches.
And you can't talk your way out of this one,
because I'm not getting confused today,
because I got my sh-t in order and I've done my research.
Okay, Neil?
You see,
we are here at this point in space-time on a human scale.
But at this point,
you a trifling ass mother-f-cker.
So expect the papers from the lawyer,
because we're parting ways.
Well,
actually...
No, no.
We are always parting ways and not parting
ways in every conceivable combination.
Many physicists, including Stephen Hawking,
now believe that there is an infinite number of universes.
It's called multiverse theory.
And it suggests that there are an infinite number of universes
in which
I didn't have sex with that white woman.
I f-cking built Nye the Science Guy.
You bitch.
It's Joey Bluntz in the morning!
Yo, Joey Bluntz here.
I want a 1.2-table seat in the wall.
Meatball!
Hey,
everybody,
man,
we still tripping on that last segment,
though.
That was crazy up in here.
That was crazy.
What's your mouth up?
Y'all are crazy.
I can't take this one.
Like, y'all dirty, but she's crazy.
Would you do that meatball?
Man,
look,
man,
I grew up in the hood,
all right?
So, no.
So he would want to,
but he can't do it because of that bad ass.
Oh!
Why y'all always clowning on meatball?
Meatball!
Who brought it up?
For real, though?
Oh, you're a lesser first-class.
Y'all got to stop playing.
Meatball! Lady J with me here, meatball.
And this is the top of the hour.
I'm Joey Bluntz.
We'll be right back.
Whoo!
...trying our new rejuvenating formula.
One thing is...
KB's 101.3.
Ah!
Oh!
We got too far!
Oh, he's out.
Just gonna sit down and relax a little bit.
Hey, watch where the f*** you going.
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.
Oh.
I didn't see you had a baby there, man.
I'm sorry.
I ain't trying to fight nobody with a baby.
Yeah, hell yeah, you won't.
Okay.
Lucky mother****er.
Huh?
Well, you're lucky I'm carrying this baby.
Sound like that.
Look, man, you need to move on, all right?
I already told you, I'm not gonna fight you.
That's what I thought,
punk.
Psst, wanna go?
Cause we can go right now, dog.
What's going on, all right?
Man, what the hell are you doing, man?
Oh, what, what?
What, what?
Trying to bob, bob and weave it.
What?
You bitch ass,
punk ass,
mother-fucker,
let's go.
Come on, man.
Come on, don't look at your boys.
Look at me, man.
Don't look at your boy.
Ow. Oh, okay, you think you hard.
All right, but you know what?
I'm gonna show you what time it is right now,
okay?
Slap me.
Right, how about this?
Huh?
Now what you gonna do, huh?
Now what you gonna do?
You ready?
Cause we can do it right now.
Cause I can take you out, man.
You're not gonna- Ow!
Oh!
Oof.
Okay.
Oh, it's on now.
That's, yep, you did.
You did.
Excuse me, I need this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need a baby.
Oh! Thank you.
Oh, yeah,
yeah.
This...
What the...
What now, man?
What now?
Let's go.
You know what?
It's not even worth it, man.
Ah!
That's what I thought.
So keep walking.
Oh, okay, that's vomit.
That is vomit.
Oh, dear.
Okay, but do I look in the camera?
No?
Oh, I do.
All right.
Like on television.
Oh!
Now knock it off, all the stupid ass, grab ass,
and touchy-feely bullsh-t.
Goddamn.
I told you they was rotten.
I am Ponybus Jackson,
principal here at Clortho.
Uh, Vince Clortho High.
Uh, this station is just a formality.
Here's a bunch of stuff that we confiscated just this week.
Stuff?
You don't have to show them that.
Here's a wand with a silencer on it.
Why?
But I ask again, why?
One out of five girls in this school
is pregnant with a demon baby.
One out of five! Okay.
Ain't no denying it.
The babies are evil.
But the mothers, they're good kids.
As we say at Clortho's,
there's never a portal that cannot be opened
with ingenuity and respect.
Now...
How you gonna be using an invisible cloak
when I can see you tagging the damn wall?
Dying bag of pixie dust?
Pfft.
Contraband?
Here's the thing.
The kids know that the only way to fly...
Wizard pepper! Unbelievable.
Get your ass out of my office.
I will turn you into a spider!
They're good kids.
Hogwarts and Clortho's, Clortho's and Hogwarts.
Go hand in hand.
The best top two wizarding schools there are.
But,
you know,
out of these two schools,
we each have our strengths.
We do score a little bit lower on
our standardized tests than Hogwarts,
but there is a cultural bias.
We may not have a huge endowment like they get over at Hogwarts.
And yes,
some of the teachers have to buy their own newt's eyes or bat wings.
One kid got transformed into a cat.
They can't even afford a changing back.
This young man's name is Jamar.
Normally,
you're not allowed to touch the students
like this when they're in human form.
But, uh,
when they're a cat, we just have at it.
Sports.
Sports!
Everybody loves sports.
It's true.
The hallways are a bluster with the conversation of awkwardness.
Half the team is back here riding mops.
We got two little niggas on Swiffer.
Lester!
When all is said and done,
the average Clortho student said,
this mother...
SHE LAUGHS
Sometimes the kids think it's cute to turn themselves into a rat.
Sneak into my office, play a little joke on me.
Who is that?
Tyrone?
Is that...
No, that's an actual rat.
MUSIC PLAYS
There he is! Hey, what's up?
Hey, man.
What's up, man?
Hey, here's the deal.
% grass-fed Japanese Kobe beef, $35 a pound.
That's what I'm talking about.
All right.
Let's grill these little homies up.
Right, all right.
Oh, man, is that ground chuck, man?
No offense,
I ain't trying to park my Bentley next to your Toyota.
Come on, man.
Oh,
you're just putting it right next to the frozen pan.
Yeah.
All right.
Relax, man.
I'm gonna cook them good.
Okay.
All right.
So, uh, how's Teresa doing?
She's good.
She's sad she couldn't be here.
You know, she's got her closing today.
You want to flash cook those because they're real lean.
You know, they're grass-fed.
So you just want to probably flip them right now.
All right.
Hey, who wants cheese on their burger?
Nobody! Nobody! Nobody wants cheese!
Anybody want a double burger?
No, nobody wants a double burger.
We're not gonna double.
That's like putting a diamond ring on a pig hoof.
I'm sorry,
but the grass that these cows ate costs more than this house.
All right.
No double burgers.
Hey.
What the hell?
You may as well just poop on that.
What?
You just ketchup-raped my Kobe burger.
This was a mistake.
This...
No. No. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
See,
this meat came all the way over here from the Pacific Ocean by boat
because the air pressure wouldn't ruin its integrity.
Wait a minute.
Give me that.
You are not worthy.
You're not worthy.
This is ridiculous.
$126,000 for this little mother...
$126,000 worth of beef.
Y'all not worthy.
Mm-hmm.
Did he take my dog?
Hey,
all I know is it's good having another brother
move into the neighborhood.
Hey, man, it's good to have you over.
And I think that you will dig this.
All right.
Hey. Huh?
Nice guitar collection.
Oh, thanks, man.
Hey, you want to hear something?
Yeah, sure.
All right.
Let's get this to his level.
Let's do this.
Well, I'm just a good old American boy
With a heart that's red, white and true
Dreaming of the girl with the red hair and freckles
And her eyes like the skies of blue Country music.
I grew up in Texas, you know, so...
All right.
Keep her safe from the homies in the wrong side of town
Where they're smoking the reefer and acting like clowns
Keep that pretty white dress from getting dirty and brown
Because that's the American way
Woohoo!
Oh,
pretty racist song.
Racist against who?
Black people.
Black people?
But I'm black.
Well,
keeping the redheaded girl away from
the homies on the wrong side of town.
Homies?
Come on, brother, there's all kinds of homies.
You know, white homies, Asian homies.
No, homies are black.
No, I think you're making them black, man.
I mean, I think that's your stuff.
You hear the twang,
and then you assume that it's racist.
But that's just what country music is like.
Look, you're gonna like this one.
You'll like this one.
All right.
Some folks wear their hats way off to the side
With their pants down low and a gun tucked inside
Take their beer by the 40 and their chicken deep-fried
I think we all know who we're talking about
The only dark I like is when I turn off the lights
The only hood I love is pointy and white
And trust you if I can't see your face at night
I think we all know who we're talking about
Wait, wait, hey.
Stop that.
That's racist.
What's what?
What is racist about it?
The only hood I love is pointy and white?
Yeah, man.
That's talking about the Klan,
man.
The Ku Klux Klan?
Are you outside of your mind?
That's traditional country music imagery, man.
Like a pickup truck or sleeping under the stars
or your dog got killed or your wife left you.
Same thing.
I would have been fine with any of those things.
What is the difference between those things and what is in the song?
They're not racial.
Hey, you know what?
Can I just say something, man?
I'm just gonna be frank.
You're getting a little,
like,
Al Sharpton,
um, ferricon on me right now, man.
Oh, my God. Are you serious?
Dude, dude, please.
Hey, can I do one more?
Let me just do one more, dog.
I absolutely promise you that this song
is not racist
and it's impossible for you to misinterpret it as such.
Okay,
it seems like you're about to sing the most racist song so far.
I'm not.
Ha-dee-la-dee-la-dee-lee
Get me a rope and find me a tree
Okay.
I'm out.
Come on, man.
Hey.
Shit.
Over here trying to sing about a tire swing.
Right off an entire genre of music.
The banjos are strumming
And the drums are banging
Let's get the boys together
And have ourselves a hangin'
Oh, damn.
Now I see it.